(Howard:)Okay, I gotta ask...
(Howard:)why are you wearing
a bow tie?
(Sheldon:)I've never applied
for a patent before.
(Sheldon:)I wanted to make
a good impression.
Oh. Is the impression that
your first name is Pee-Wee?
(chuckling)
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, you're an engineer.
(Sheldon:)End of joke, burn.
(Attorney:)Come on in, fellas.
(Howard:)See, he's not wearing a tie.
(Leonard:)Well, he's
a patent attorney.
(Leonard:)Maybe his tie is pending.
(Attorney:)So, I've reviewed
your paperwork,
(Attorney:)and it seems like
we've got everything we need
(Attorney:)to file a patent
(Attorney:)for your infinite
persistence gyroscope.
That's great!
Excellent.
(Leonard:)So what happens next?
(Attorney:)Well, the legal team
needs to review
(Attorney:)existing patents
to avoid overlap.
(Howard:)Oh, I don't think
there will be.
Yes, we did
our own search.
(Attorney:)That's nice, but I think ours
might be a bit more thorough.